[{"answer": "For what", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Music", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Music", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Is that why you're wearing a mask", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Tell me, my friend, what good is an actor that plays his part to an empty theatre", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Nor do I.  That's why you are here. I need you, Evey.  I need someone to listen", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Nor do I.  That's why you are here. I need you, Evey.  I need someone to listen", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes.  Yes, to my music", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Five", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Room five", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Perfectly", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "that place prevails", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No, I", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh god, I don't", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'm saying that perhaps I don't know you as well as I thought I did", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, I am asking for some goddamn results", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Is this what you consider,", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Mr. my friend, I want the producers, writers, and actors of that", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You know me too well now", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I'm going to fulfill an old promise", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Careful", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I told you.  I'm going to finish what was started four hundred years ago", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend!  Of course.  Of course!  It makes such perfect sense", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No!  There is no mistake", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No!  There is no mistake", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Who?  Who are these people?  They must be detained immediately. Whatever they saw or whatever they think they saw is subordinate to the truth and that truth is that my friend is the terrorist and the terrorist is dead", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I know, Leader.  I know the way a woman knows", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Proof", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I did it, my friend.  I did it, didn't I", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Tonight", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Of course, I'll be back.  You don't think you can be rid of me now, do you", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I promise", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't understand", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I promise", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I promise", "docId": "V-for-Vendetta.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "V, you are not going anywhere", "qsentId": 36}]